http://www.susanvaughan.com/privacy-policy.html

EDITING
PRIVACY POLICY Susan Vaughan operates the susanvaughan.com website, which provides information related to the author Susan Vaughan.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of personal Information if anyone signs up for Susan Vaughan's newsletter or enter any sponsored contests.If you choose to sign up for Susan Vaughan's newsletter or enter sponsored contests, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The personal Information that we collect are used for providing information and updating subscribers/contestants only. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseTo deliver newsletters and Susan Vaughan-related messages, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name and email address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our business;To provide the business-related services on our behalf;To perform business-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our website is used.We want to inform our visitors that these third parties have access to your personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links to Other SitesOur website may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.Children's PrivacyOur Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 18. In the case we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at: shvaughan.author @gmail.com (with no spaces).
Copyright Susan Vaughan 2015
Check out Warner Vaughan's clocks at www.gullwoodclocks.com.Privacy Policy
